[{"id": "59e801f2de59ea584496fe94", "question": "In which state would you find the \"House of the Seven Gables\"?", "answer": "Massachusetts", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd969ce23c87fd04dd15e0d", "question": "What was Thomas Edison's nickname?", "answer": "The Wizard of Menlo Park", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab4d", "question": "What canal connects Lake Ontario and Lake Erie?", "answer": "Welland Canal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fecdb4dec223966ae8f88f2", "question": "In \"Ghostbusters,\" what prompts Dr. Peter Venkman to say, \"Well, there's something you don't see every day\"?", "answer": "Stay Puft Marshmallow Man", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cff", "question": "In which movie did Cassandra Gava portray a witch?", "answer": "Conan the Barbarian", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339446", "question": "Which \"Friends\" star previously starred in a sitcom titled \"Top of the Heap\"?", "answer": "Matt LeBlanc", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd66638a5bfecdd737e0867", "question": "What color is second from the top in a rainbow?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9f02bff048f679a45aa98", "question": "Philophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Love", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390fc", "question": "What year did Frederick Forsyth publish the novel \"The Deceiver\"?", "answer": "1991", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffa43aac73aa70ea0b70b19", "question": "In which country can you find a beach that resembles a \"golden horn\"?", "answer": "Croatia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd96fc323c87fd04dd15e45", "question": "What are the earliest known Christmas tree decorations?", "answer": "Apples", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b726", "question": "What seafood is considered a Christmas favourite in Paris, France?", "answer": "Oysters", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a07f", "question": "Which actor was the first to play Robin Hood on television?", "answer": "Patrick Troughton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea489bff048f679a45abb1", "question": "If you throw a ball in the air, what curve does it trace out?", "answer": "Parabola", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e20", "question": "\"Songbird\" is a book about what jazz singer's remarkable posthumous career?", "answer": "Eva Cassidy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7dc", "question": "What are the four railways in the standard version of Monopoly?", "answer": "The B&O, Pennsylvania, Reading, Short Line", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f2", "question": "What note is the highest string of a violin usually tuned to?", "answer": "E", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c836", "question": "Before the 2004 launch of Space Ship One, who was the last American ever to go into space alone?", "answer": "Gordon Cooper", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a4d9a9f08b8581f80b092be", "question": "Whose concert was the target of a terrorist attack in May, 2017, in Manchester, UK?", "answer": "Ariana Grande\u2019s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eae20f83302ff91e46484", "question": "Which creature was the Egyptian God Horus identified with?", "answer": "Falcon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b165", "question": "What year did basketball become an official Olympic event?", "answer": "1936", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59cdb1ff65ff7d326b622a6f", "question": "Petrology the study of what?", "answer": "Rocks", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59071d593745b36be73039d6", "question": "What operation brought over 1,500 German scientists, engineers and technicians following the end of World War II to the US to aid in military research?", "answer": "Operation Paperclip", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c97", "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Mockingbird Heights?", "answer": "The Munsters", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d7", "question": "Who were Bobby Hatfield and Bill Medley?", "answer": "The Righteous Brothers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338985", "question": "What is the only nationality mentioned in the song \"The Twelve Days of Christmas\"?", "answer": "French", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b0", "question": "What movie gives Jack Nicholson the chance to yell at Tom Cruise: \"You can't handle the truth!\"?", "answer": "A Few Good Men", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a0a", "question": "What musician plays pinball against Roger Daltrey in the 1975 film version of The Who's \"Tommy\"?", "answer": "Elton John", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1d9", "question": "What is Merlin's owl name in Disney's film \"The Sword in the Stone\"?", "answer": "Archimedes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b003", "question": "In 1810, New York overtook what city as America's most populated city?", "answer": "Philadelphia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6ed", "question": "What is a single piece of coiled DNA is known as?", "answer": "Chromosome", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ad", "question": "Who recorded the international hit single \"Poker Face\" in 2008?", "answer": "Lady Gaga", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4e2", "question": "Which country covers an entire continent?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd69", "question": "According to the 1940s jingle, after what two men pitched did Boston Braves fans \"pray for rain\"?", "answer": "Spahn and Sain", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c967", "question": "What is the fear of flying called?", "answer": "Aviatophobia or pteromerhanophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ae0", "question": "Which novel features a character named Hester Prynne?", "answer": "Scarlett Letter", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3d6", "question": "Hyperopia is the scientific name for what eye condition?", "answer": "Farsightedness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e8", "question": "What does M.C. stand for in M.C. Escher's name?", "answer": "Maurits Cornelis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca9a", "question": "What is the Larynx often referred to as?", "answer": "Voice box", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c53b", "question": "How many tentacles does a squid have?", "answer": "Ten", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c03b", "question": "How many stars are on the flag of New Zealand?", "answer": "Four", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ca3c7944f0f6af5b066631", "question": "Ranidaphobia is a fear of what?", "answer": "Frogs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdab3a30b8cce1e6fda7046", "question": "What is \"jaggery\", regularly used in Indian cooking?", "answer": "Sugar", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59071d2c3745b36be73039d5", "question": "What Soviet operation forced over 2,000 scientists and engineers to relocate from East Germany to Russia to work on missile design and production?", "answer": "Operation Osoaviakhim", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f54", "question": "What was the name of Bilbo and Frodo Baggins' hobbit hole?", "answer": "Bag End", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d5a", "question": "Where was Wonder Woman born?", "answer": "Paradise Island", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe775beeec85e375820b310", "question": "What is the world's oldest desert?", "answer": "Namibia Desert", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2bd", "question": "How many seasons were there of the TV show \"30 Rock\"?", "answer": "7", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ec25cd8dc25ca9e12ef642", "question": "What fraternity do the Lewis and Gilbert join in the 1984 film \"Revenge of the Nerds\"?", "answer": "Lambda Lambda Lambda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8ab", "question": "Which middle layer of a tooth contains the root canals?", "answer": "The dentin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cb70c02f96e155acab35d28", "question": "What is Chiroptophobia?", "answer": "Fear of Bats", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a301", "question": "Randy Poffo, who was a pitchman for Slim Jim, was better known by what name?", "answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c63c", "question": "What number is indicated by the Roman Numeral \"D\"?", "answer": "500", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b59b", "question": "What do you call a group of Geese?", "answer": "Gaggle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ae5", "question": "Who played Ike Turner in the 1993 Tina Turner biopic \"What's Love Got To Do With It?\"", "answer": "Laurence Fishburne", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f04", "question": "What author created the character of Sherlock Holmes?", "answer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3a63ff048f679a45ab2b", "question": "What does the human lacrimal gland produce?", "answer": "Tears", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8c5", "question": "How many stars are in the Big Dipper?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cdf", "question": "How do Ben and Elaine get away from the church at the end of \"The Graduate\"?", "answer": "By bus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe0dc1afcbed638185eaa0c", "question": "Where can you find a museum dedicated to the history of bread?", "answer": "Ulm, Germany", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ee", "question": "What organization in the Harry Potter series is named after Dumbledore's patronus?", "answer": "Order of the Phoenix", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caf0", "question": "What is the condition resulting from prolonged muscular or mental activity?", "answer": "Fatigue", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391fe", "question": "In which movie did Eddie Murphy play a character named Prince Akeem?", "answer": "Coming to America", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e4", "question": "Which popular musician co-wrote the song \"I'm afraid of Americans\" with David Bowie?", "answer": "Brian Eno", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d22", "question": "Patty Duke won an Oscar in 1963 for portraying what popular author?", "answer": "Helen Keller", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c273", "question": "What is June's birthstone?", "answer": "Pearl", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ae1", "question": "Hamlet was the Prince of which country?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133909b", "question": "In Greek mythology, what is Demeter the goddess of what?", "answer": "Harvest and agriculture", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc1c", "question": "What was New York Yankees original name?", "answer": "New York Highlanders", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ad7e737b24f84e0b9f9ffb7", "question": "Whose voice, made popular by the Star Wars franchies, narrated the 1995 film \"Judge Dredd\"?", "answer": "James Earl Jones", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b665", "question": "What was the first foot product invented by Dr. William Matthias Scholl?", "answer": "Arch supports", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a729", "question": "Springfield is the capital of which state?", "answer": "Illinois", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b69e", "question": "What type of alcohol is typically used to make a mint julep?", "answer": "Bourbon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe6998f20565ad31a57c748", "question": "What were the names of the Doberman Pinschers on \"Magnum P.I.\"?", "answer": "Zeus and Apollo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c8d4fbde8045e48466e1", "question": "Why do some plants send chemical signals to bugs?", "answer": "Signal for help -- Leafy tobacco plants send a chemical signal to wasps, who will seek out caterpillars eating the leaves.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b847", "question": "What was the original name of \"Skype\"?", "answer": "Sky peer-to-peer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339db9", "question": "How does the hook-handed Woody Harrelson lose his right hand in the film \"Kingpin\"?", "answer": "In a bowling ball return", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5c90d5cb52800b05cac20f1e", "question": "As of 2018, what is the best selling video game console of all time?", "answer": "PlayStation 2", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a991", "question": "In what mountain range is Mount Ansel Adams?", "answer": "The Sierra Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397ea", "question": "Who played the sadistic sheriff in Clint Eastwood\u2019s \"Unforgiven\"?", "answer": "Gene Hackman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a553a03e1c6f9840ba31a6", "question": "In which popular 1950s film is a character played by Audrey Hepburn given 24 hours to do as she pleases in the eternal city?", "answer": "Roman Holiday", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ca3e3244f0f6af5b066647", "question": "In mathematics which prefix refers to 10 to the power of minus 21?", "answer": "Zepto", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c111", "question": "Elvis Stojko was an ice skating champion hailing from what?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133948b", "question": "Who directed the movie \"Leaving Las Vegas\"?", "answer": "Mike Figgis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8cee294b094db915830ab", "question": "Who is credited with creating McDonald\u2019s\u2019 Big Mac?", "answer": "Jim Delligatti", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a443", "question": "What river does the Tower Bridge in London cross?", "answer": "Thames", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bafb", "question": "What word is used to describe one and a half ounces of liquor?", "answer": "Jigger", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339382", "question": "What brand of cigarettes does Chris have in the movie \"Stand By Me\"?", "answer": "Winston", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febbbbb7e83c707845b214a", "question": "What special title does Anthony Hopkins possess in real life?", "answer": "Sir (Sir Anthony Hopkins was knighted by Queen Elizabeth in 1993, two years after the release of \"the Silence of the Lambs\".)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5952413d736d4be723796b61", "question": "Which superhero was created by Mike Young, as a way to help his child sleep at night?", "answer": "SuperTed", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015eba4fe83fe1f2a824bf9", "question": "In what country was the phrase \"trick or treat\" first used?", "answer": "Canada -- The first recorded use of the term was in 1927 in Lethbridge, Alberta.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c088", "question": "What is Plutophobia the fear of?", "answer": "Wealth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b845", "question": "What is a perfect score in bowling?", "answer": "300", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fc8424f78d18506ae1fe48b", "question": "In the Western Hemisphere, what is the most western capital?", "answer": "Mexico City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b083", "question": "In what year did \"Mad Magazine\" debut?", "answer": "1952", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c135", "question": "Which significant beverage did John Pemberton invent in 1886?", "answer": "Coca-Cola", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339208", "question": "What pop star posed naked and pregnant on the August 2006 cover of Harper's Bazaar?", "answer": "Britney Spears", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "597cdaa5e347d002c297e4d5", "question": "What nationality is Yehudi Menuhin?", "answer": "American", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdc1375469bb8041d07a07f", "question": "What did the \"lemon campaign\" advertise in the 60's?", "answer": "Volkswagen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe36e750ada16518afdc045", "question": "What city has traffic lights shaped like Hershey's Kisses?", "answer": "Hershey, Pennsylvania", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af08", "question": "Who replaced Colin Powell as Secretary of State under president George W. Bush?", "answer": "Condoleezza Rice", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f60", "question": "What supermodel plays the bride in Guns N' Roses' \"November Rain\" video?", "answer": "Stephanie Seymour", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e910021d7247dfc0fa0030c", "question": "The first U.S. state park was created in which state?", "answer": "New York", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388fc", "question": "What fictional Harvard professor appears in Dan Brown novels including the \"The Da Vinci Code\"?", "answer": "Robert Langdon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59db771b0ab2c8f322317feb", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", who or what is Santa's Little Helper?", "answer": "The Simpsons' pet dog", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ab", "question": "Who does Emma Watson play in the Harry Potter films?", "answer": "Hermione", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a093", "question": "What 1970's film came from a Pink Floyd tune?", "answer": "The Wall", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe76935eec85e375820b2ae", "question": "Socotra is an island belonging to what country?", "answer": "Yemen", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b7", "question": "From which movie did the phrase \"You can't handle the truth!\" originate?", "answer": "A Few Good Men", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339283", "question": "Who won part 1 of the final \"Head Of Household\" competition in season 14 of the TV show \"Big Brother\"?", "answer": "Dan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc84", "question": "The 2007 rule banning suspended NFL players from signing with the CFL was named for what player?", "answer": "Ricky Williams", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bac5", "question": "What year was National Geographic magazine first published?", "answer": "1888", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e5f0d67d274615ecf514533", "question": "What U.S. President's family home was known as the \"Sherwood Forest Plantation\"?", "answer": "John Tyler", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9ac", "question": "In 1983, who became the first African American to win the Miss America Pageant?", "answer": "Vanessa Williams", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b584", "question": "What is the name for Argentinean cowboys?", "answer": "Gauchos", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a29d", "question": "Who starred as the male lead in the Alfred Hitchcock film \"To Catch a Thief\"?", "answer": "Cary Grant", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb3c", "question": "What NHL team won the 2011 Stanley Cup in hockey?", "answer": "Boston Bruins", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5a3", "question": "How many ounces are there in a pound?", "answer": "16", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff51c95ff04d658268c9318", "question": "In the Bible, who is the wife of Boaz?", "answer": "Ruth", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dc3", "question": "\"Petunia, No. 2\" was the first of the giant flower canvases painted by what artist?", "answer": "Georgia O'Keeffe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5f164e6af9b80650dbe7f933", "question": "What color is the \"Time stone\" in the 2017 Marvel Legacy relaunch?", "answer": "Green", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6002435d4be4723ccac22195", "question": "In William Shakespeare\u2019s \"A Midsummer Night\u2019s Dream\", what is the name of the King of the Fairies?", "answer": "Oberon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca2e", "question": "Paper and Mud Dauber are types of what?", "answer": "Wasp", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9d1", "question": "What is the capital of the US state North Carolina?", "answer": "Raleigh", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a4a96f561d1b4d384d5d67e", "question": "What character first appeared in the film \"The Wise Little Hen\"?", "answer": "Donald Duck", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ffe", "question": "What is the occupation of Mary Poppins?", "answer": "Nanny", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392a7", "question": "Who provided the voice for Mickey Mouse from 1928 to 1946?", "answer": "Walt Disney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c811", "question": "What spectral class does our sun belong to?", "answer": "G", "category": "science"}, {"id": "591c3508815febcc896f9258", "question": "In which country would you find the motor racing circuit called Kyalami?", "answer": "South Africa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e147a756ca6dac04a20ca4f", "question": "When did Thomas Jefferson purchase the territory of Louisiana?", "answer": "1803", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e00", "question": "Whose tombstone bears the inscription \"Everybody Loves Somebody Sometime\"?", "answer": "Dean Martin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ae8629c7f28483af1e7fdc7", "question": "What country has the highest average rainfall in the world?", "answer": "India", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59ded077ea2747c8aff16d28", "question": "Ireland's River Shannon flows into which ocean?", "answer": "Atlantic Ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe768b2eec85e375820b2a5", "question": "What does the orange color on Ireland's flag represent?", "answer": "Protestants", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa95", "question": "In which forest does the Danube River rise?", "answer": "Black Forest", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d474e4f8e329de4f8778a1", "question": "The \"Associated Powers\" was the original proposed name of what organization?", "answer": "The United Nations", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c01e", "question": "Who invented basketball?", "answer": "James Naismith", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339482", "question": "Who directed the 1969 movie \"The Wild Bunch\"?", "answer": "Sam Peckinpah", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefa5ea6ce05a3942286ec6", "question": "In the film \"Dragnet,\" who played Sgt. Joe Friday?", "answer": "Dan Aykroyd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cb09", "question": "What do pumpkins grow on?", "answer": "Vines", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133977e", "question": "Other than the Lord of the Rings trilogy, for what movie was Peter Jackson nominated an Oscar?", "answer": "Heavenly Creatures", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397ac", "question": "What A-Team cast member was once a bodyguard for Muhammad Ali and Leon Spinks?", "answer": "Mr. T", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe529341bf59ab7d2e38100", "question": "What would you get if you were to receive a Xoloitzcuintli as a gift?", "answer": "A dog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa2c", "question": "Which is the largest lake by area in the British Isles?", "answer": "Lough Neagh", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe69c6f20565ad31a57c76c", "question": "The \"Era of Good Feelings\" is associated with the administration of which president?", "answer": "James Monroe", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba52", "question": "What black and white bird is the official state bird of Minnesota?", "answer": "Common Loon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395ea", "question": "In The Simpsons, who said: \" Good evening, everyone, and welcome to a wonderful evening of theater and picking up after yourselves", "answer": "Principal Skinner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbb3", "question": "Who was head coach of the Notre Dame college football team from 1918 to 1930?", "answer": "Knute Rockne", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a134", "question": "What is the name of Olive Oyl's father?", "answer": "Cole Oyl", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef93fe6ce05a3942286e93", "question": "What show did \"TV Guide\" name the \"best TV show of all time\" in 2002?", "answer": "\"Seinfeld\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60136f681381754895396375", "question": "Where is Superman\u2019s Fortress of Solitude?", "answer": "Arctic Circle -- Although he's had different bachelor pads, he classically heads to the Arctic Circle when he wants to be alone.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe771c8eec85e375820b2ff", "question": "What is New York's state bird?", "answer": "Bluebird", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395da", "question": "In The Simpsons, what is the name of Ned Flanders' specialty store?", "answer": "The Leftorium", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b524e662d71a53650ff5", "question": "Born Edgar Poe, where did the middle name Allan come from?", "answer": "It was his adoptive parents' name.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "590722143745b36be73039fc", "question": "Who wrote the 1996 novel \"Certain Poor Shepherds: A Christmas Tale\"?", "answer": "Elizabeth Marshall Thomas", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febb63c7e83c707845b2125", "question": "What is a hybrid of a cow and bison called?", "answer": "Beefalo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7b2", "question": "In what city is Purdue University located?", "answer": "West Lafayette, IN", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ab99daa21a8909e5c332d42", "question": "What was the original working title of the movie \"Help!\", starring the Beatles?", "answer": "Eight Arms To Hold You", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339218", "question": "What is the theme song of the TV show \"Friends\" called?", "answer": "I'll Be There for You by The Rembrandts", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b880", "question": "What four colors are used in four-color process printing?", "answer": "Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, Black", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a459", "question": "The Bermuda Triangle is located in what ocean?", "answer": "Atlantic Ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe3f0798b5801b8f54a7fbb", "question": "Vienna's famous Sch\u00f6nbrunn Palace is home to the world's oldest what?", "answer": "Zoo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cac6", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for tin?", "answer": "Sn", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1bb", "question": "Who is the lead singer of the English band \"Yes\"?", "answer": "Jon Anderson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e59", "question": "What literary work inspired Neutral Milk Hotel's \"Holland 1945\" song?", "answer": "The Diary of Anne Frank", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea32aeff048f679a45aae9", "question": "How often do your taste buds regenerate on average?", "answer": "Every ten days", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a025", "question": "What is the name of the female field reporter for Channel 5 News in the TV show \"Family Guy\"?", "answer": "Tricia Takanawa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa58", "question": "Which is the largest of the Canary Islands?", "answer": "Tenerife", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133916e", "question": "What the are the first names of \"The Brothers Coen\"?", "answer": "Joel and Ethan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd665dca5bfecdd737e0863", "question": "What is the most expensive aircraft in the world?", "answer": "Air Force One", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a314", "question": "What year did \"Video Killed the Radio Star\" become the first music video on MTV?", "answer": "1981", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133913d", "question": "What was the Roman equivalent of the Greek god Poseidon?", "answer": "Neptune", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339724", "question": "What is Elton John's real name?", "answer": "Reginald Dwight", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd85", "question": "What type of animal is the Japanese monster, Kamacuras?", "answer": "Praying mantis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febd4747e83c707845b215c", "question": "What is Forrest Gump's IQ?", "answer": "75", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe12f17e39efa6330e0fed6", "question": "Where is Great Sand Dunes National Park?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a74", "question": "What was the name of the high school attended by Archie Andrews and his comic-book friends?", "answer": "Riverdale", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ec7", "question": "Who was fired from the Interior Department in 1865 for having written \"Leaves of Grass\"?", "answer": "Walt Whitman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe8b28501dd7bf43be5e79f", "question": "What does your moon sign represent?", "answer": "Your subconscious and emotions", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fffa74c73838c5c8a417f36", "question": "What is the fear of long words known as?", "answer": "Hippopotomostrosesquippedaliophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fefc2176ce05a3942286f19", "question": "In the film \"Dirty Harry,\" what gun does Harry Callahan carry?", "answer": "Smith and Wesson Model 29", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae06", "question": "Which two tools are depicted on the former Soviet Union's flag?", "answer": "Hammer and sickle", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5bbc954160f0007efaba0e61", "question": "What is entamaphobia?", "answer": "Fear of doors", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac9a", "question": "What is the FBI motto?", "answer": "Fidelity, Bravery and Integrity", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392cf", "question": "What film stars Bruce Willis as a plastic surgeon Ernest Menville?", "answer": "Death Becomes Her", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133996d", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", whose mother did Comic Book Guy once date?", "answer": "Principal Skinner's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b4c701dd7bf43be5e7c7", "question": "How old do you have to be to serve in the U.S. Senate?", "answer": "30 years", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca37", "question": "Which element is third on the periodic table?", "answer": "Lithium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396ba", "question": "Which Seinfeld character takes his shirt off when he visits the toilet?", "answer": "George Costanza", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b265", "question": "Who did the American media nickname \"Muttnik\"?", "answer": "Laika", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8b4", "question": "Leda orbits what planet of the solar system?", "answer": "Jupiter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58f167cdf7c52aae91cc07be", "question": "The Bijagos Archipelago lie off which country's mainland?", "answer": "Guinea-Bissau", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f53", "question": "Who is Dinah, whom Alice thinks about nostalgically as she falls down the rabbit hole to Wonderland?", "answer": "Her cat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "597cd518e347d002c297e4b4", "question": "Which book did James Fenimore Cooper publish in 1826?", "answer": "The Last of the Mohicans", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ecae269790ded87bb38fd88", "question": "In biology, what does RNA stand for?", "answer": "Ribonucleic Acid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339316", "question": "In the 1986 movie \"Aliens\", how many years was Ripley adrift in space?", "answer": "57", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394eb", "question": "What is the name of the Green Hornet's car?", "answer": "Black Beauty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5be580815415ba52ed6f0ab5", "question": "Approximately, how many seconds comprise a day?", "answer": "86400", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8d2", "question": "What is isolophobia the fear of?", "answer": "Being alone", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c503", "question": "What actually is a shooting star?", "answer": "A meteor", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600244004be4723ccac2219f", "question": "Snowball and Napoleon are pigs who appear in which George Orwell novel?", "answer": "\"Animal Farm\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339794", "question": "In which US state did the Charleston originate?", "answer": "South Carolina", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af25961b63e5727cf5a484d", "question": "Celine Dion's \"My Heart Will Go On\" song was featured as the main theme song to which 1990's movie?", "answer": "Titanic", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fc0", "question": "What is the third movement of a symphony called?", "answer": "Minuet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5937ea1808d98002fdd6339f", "question": "Stephen King's \"The Shining\" is set at which hotel?", "answer": "Overlook Hotel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c3e9930ebfabb9c85d8a970", "question": "What film starred Rosie O'Donnell, Rita Wilson and Meg Ryan?", "answer": "Sleepless in Seattle", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc90", "question": "Who is the only founding member of both the International Surfing and Swimming Halls of Fame?", "answer": "Duke Kahanamoku", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58dba39f874c93a3298b213e", "question": "Who was nicknamed La Pucelle d'Orl\u00e9ans?", "answer": "Joan of Arc", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937eed608d98002fdd633d9", "question": "From which musical did \"One Night in Bangkok Makes a Hard Man Humble\" and \"I Know Him So Well\" come?", "answer": "Chess", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6007826ebd51d85e222ab658", "question": "Who were the models that posed for Grant Wood's famous painting, American Gothic?", "answer": "He asked his\u00a0sister Nan\u00a0to wear his mother's apron and pin while posing, and recruited his\u00a062-year-old dentist\u00a0to model the man.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c519", "question": "What lemon-scented oil is derived from dried grasses and used as an insect repellent?", "answer": "Citronella", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4ea", "question": "How much money do you start a game of standard \"Monopoly\" with?", "answer": "$1500", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb12", "question": "In what year did Jimmy Buffett open his first Margaritaville restaurant?", "answer": "1985", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a7f", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Dragon Seed\"?", "answer": "Pearl S. Buck", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fec8588ec223966ae8f8806", "question": "What is the first \"Friday the 13th\" movie in which Jason dons his iconic mask?", "answer": "\"Friday the 13th Part III\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8f9df01dd7bf43be5e84f", "question": "As of 2020, what is the name of the largest submarine in the world?", "answer": "Dmitriy Donskoy, TK-208", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b358dd55db0d66a186cb564", "question": "Where would you most often come across a chicane?", "answer": "On a motor racing track", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5af25ca1b63e5727cf5a4861", "question": "In which city was Tupac Shakur shot dead?", "answer": "Las Vegas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6000f1379a72b906b34e3d02", "question": "What is the largest constellation in the sky?", "answer": "Hydra -- Hydra covers about 1,303 square degrees, which is equal to roughly 3% of the entire celestial sphere.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "592eb04ef83302ff91e4649b", "question": "What time period does the 1972 film \"The Godfather\" span?", "answer": "1945 to 1955", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad85", "question": "What decade saw the first US postage stamp issued?", "answer": "1840s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338989", "question": "Who conducted the Philadelphia Orchestra and shook hands with Mickey Mouse in \"Fantasia\"?", "answer": "Leopold Stokowski", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe6a77020565ad31a57c7e8", "question": "Which Wild West figure was nicknamed \"little sure-shot\"?", "answer": "Annie Oakley", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339512", "question": "Who was the first actor in history to decline an Oscar?", "answer": "George C. Scott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338be9", "question": "Which instrument does the Leader of an orchestra play?", "answer": "Violin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb7b", "question": "In the 1890's, what type of cheese did a California man named David Jacks introduce?", "answer": "Monterey Jack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a486", "question": "Mount Etna is located on which island?", "answer": "Sicily", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c797", "question": "Which scientist is credited with being the first one to isolate DNA material?", "answer": "Friedrich Miescher", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac6d", "question": "What purpose did the Colosseum serve when first built?", "answer": "Amphitheatre", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5d5", "question": "What is a googol?", "answer": "10 to the 100th power", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a83e", "question": "Virginia's Shenandoah River is the largest tributary of what other river?", "answer": "The Potomac", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c36c", "question": "What sign of the zodiac is the first air sign of the calender year?", "answer": "Aquarius", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac15", "question": "The Union of the Comoros is located on the northern end of which water channel?", "answer": "Mozambique Channel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fde4966c6c6b019850c9a6f", "question": "Easter was named from what Anglo-Saxon goddess?", "answer": "Eostre", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff14036b0ee8c595b6d3997", "question": "The Last Supper mural originally included which body part of Christ that has since been removed?", "answer": "Feet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b458", "question": "Who is typically referred to as \"The Father of History\"?", "answer": "Herodotus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391f6", "question": "The Dude from \"The Big Lebowski\" liked to drink what?", "answer": "White Russians", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac84", "question": "Whose tomb did Howard Carter discover in 1922?", "answer": "Tutankhamun's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff6", "question": "What is an eyrie?", "answer": "The nest of a bird of prey", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f164eaaf9b80650dbe7f936", "question": "What color is the \"Mind stone\" in the 2017 Marvel Legacy relaunch?", "answer": "Yellow", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad9dcfae748bb36357acddf", "question": "In the original \"Oregon Trail\" game, made in 1971, what were the four infectious diseases that could kill members of your party?", "answer": "Typhoid, Cholera, Measles, Dysentery", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c818", "question": "In what part of the body would you find chyme?", "answer": "The stomach", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd0d", "question": "What was the original brand of cereal whose mascot was Crazy Craving?", "answer": "Honeycomb", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febb0737e83c707845b2104", "question": "Which two gems are different colors of the same mineral?", "answer": "Ruby and sapphire", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7a3", "question": "What mountain chain extends from western Canada down through Northern California?", "answer": "The Cascades", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a83d", "question": "In the first Punic War, Rome and Carthage fought over possession of what Mediterranean island?", "answer": "Sicily", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2d1", "question": "What military legend was nicknamed \"Cump\"?", "answer": "William Tecumseh Sherman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "596dfb90cf3977a46e7ce44a", "question": "The average person has over 1,460 of what each year?", "answer": "Dreams", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd823bfd0de9af39e9d46b2", "question": "What university was Dwight D. Eisenhower president of?", "answer": "Columbia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6010c6220775fa611bce67cf", "question": "What was the original name of Chicago's Willis Tower?", "answer": "Sears Tower -- Sears Tower, the former home to Sears Roebuck and Company, was the tallest building in the world from 1973 to 1998.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398a4", "question": "Who released the albums \"At Folsom Prison\" and \"At San Quentin\"?", "answer": "Johnny Cash", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "591c355b815febcc896f925b", "question": "The northernmost point in mainland Australia is on what geographic feature?", "answer": "Cape York", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58ab145dbaab681b09292173", "question": "What year did Volkswagen introduce the Golf GTI?", "answer": "1976", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5af25d36b63e5727cf5a4863", "question": "What is the name of 1992 hit single by the band \"Shakespears Sister\"?", "answer": "Stay", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b918e662d71a5365102c", "question": "\"The Color Purple\" begins, \"You better not tell nobody but\" who?", "answer": "God", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4e1", "question": "What do you get when you mix scotch, sweet vermouth and angostura bitters?", "answer": "A Rob Roy", "category": "general"}]